<dashboard>
  <label>Getting Started</label>
  <description>References to learn more about how to use the product</description>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
        <h1>Splunk Documentation</h1>
        Splunk Documentation is one of the best places to learn how to do almost anything in Splunk. <br/>
        Many times you can search within the documentation website or you can search in Google to find the docs you are looking for.<br/>
        If you use Community Slack, you can also use some very helpful SlackBot commands to find documentation <br/>
        Make sure you mark down if the documentation was helpful and any feedback you might have on the bottom of the page, our docs team loves it! <br/>
        The <b>
          <a href="https://docs.splunk.com/Documentation/Splunk/latest/SearchReference/WhatsInThisManual" target="_blank">Search Reference Manual</a>
        </b> is a great starting point to learn SPL!
      </html>
    </panel>
    <panel>
      <html>
        <h1>Splunk Answers and Community Slack</h1>
        The Splunk Community is incredibly supportive and helpful - pick their brains!<br/>
        As an internal Splunker, you should already be able to login to <b>
          <a href="https://splunk-usergroups.slack.com/" target="_blank">Community Slack</a>
        </b>
        <br/>
        There are SO MANY channels available, so make sure you find the topics you're interested in and join in the conversation!<br/>
        <b>
          <a href="https://answers.splunk.com/" target="_blank">Splunk Answers</a>
        </b> uses your Splunk credentials, as well!<br/>
        If you have the answer to a question on there, don't be shy! Don't be shy to also ask questions.
      </html>
    </panel>
  </row>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
        <h1>Splunk All The Things!!</h1>

        This app was created with the intention of allowing users the ability to check on their own permissions/capabilities and what apps and indexes they have access to, as well as all available indexes and what roles are required to search them.<br/>
        <br/>
        What you need to do to set this app up:
        <br/>
        <b>#####LOOKUPS#####</b>
        <br/>
        <b>lookups/index_descriptions.csv</b><br/>
          ◦ This lookup includes all of the indexes available to search as well as a brief description. <br/>
          ◦ To grab a list of all indexes, run the saved search: index_information. See SAVED SEARCHES for more information. <br/>
          ◦ It is best practice to update the lookup table every time a new index is created<br/>
            There could be an alert in place when an index exists that is not in this lookup (future enhancement)<br/>
        <br/>

        <b>#####EVENTTYPES#####</b>
        <br/>
        <b>default/eventtypes.conf</b><br/>
          ◦ This is not needed for the functionality of the dashboards, however it can be helpful when searching data.<br/>
          ◦ These eventtypes are various teams/groups/etc. that own various hosts. The purpose of them is so that users can more easily find data owners/subject matter experts. <br/>
          ◦ The reason for using eventtypes is so that it can be a search string when there are multiple hosts belonging to one group. If there is only one host, it can be defined in tags.conf<br/>
          ◦ There is an example in eventtypes.conf of the format.<br/>
        <br/>

        <b>#####TAGS#####</b>
        <br/>
        <b>default/tags.conf</b><br/>
          ◦ This is not needed for the functionality of the dashboards, however it can be helpful when searching data.<br/>
          ◦ These tags include the data owner department and email addresses for the various hosts identified in eventtypes.conf<br/>
          ◦ As stated in the eventtypes.conf section, if there is only one host and eventtypes aren't needed, it can all be defined solely in tags.conf<br/>
          ◦ There are examples of both formats in tags.conf<br/>
        <br/>

        What else to know?
        <br/>
        <b>#####SAVED SEARCHES#####</b>
        <br/>
        <b>default/savedsearches.conf</b><br/>
          <b>index_information</b><br/>
            ◦ This saved search creates a lookup called index_information.csv<br/>
            ◦ You may need to edit the search to include/exclude specific splunk_servers as necessary, to fit your environments needs<br/>
            ◦ This lookup is used in the Index Overview dashboard<br/>
            ◦ This search is scheduled to run once a day
      </html>
    </panel>
  </row>
</dashboard>